Erich Maria Remarque Papers, 1918-2000 (bulk 1950s - 1980s) MSS.095
Fales Library and Special Collections
- 2003 Accretion
  - Series X: Objects, 252723
    Series X: Objects consists of a handbag and portrait locket belonging to Paulette Goddard
    - Handbag with studs spelling "PAULETTE", undated; 252727 (Box 52, Object ID: 095.2.0001)
    - Portrait resembling Paulette Goddard by Ruby Walker Usher on [brass] locket, undated; 252728 (Box 52, Object ID: 095.2.0002)
  - OVERSIZE Series I: Literary properties, 252730
    - Subseries B: Arch of Triumph, circa 2000; 257101
      - Arch of Triumph Poster- Takarazuka musical stage adaptation, [2000]; 257102 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Arch of Triumph- Film Ad, [undated]; 257103 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Subseries D: Heaven has no favorites, 257104
      - "Zurcher Woche" [German language newspaper] - with excerpt from "Geborgtes Leben", March 11, 1960; 257105 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Subseries E: The Homecoming of Enoch J. Jones, 257106
      - "Die Heimkehr des Enoch J. Jones"- [poster], [undated]; 257107 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Subseries G: The Last Station, 257108
      - "Die Letzte Station" at Renaissance Theater Berlin- [photocopy of 1956 original], [undated]; 257109 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Subseries M: Spark of Life, 257110
      - Uncorrected Proofs- "Spark of Life", August 9, 1951; 257111 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Subseries N: Three Comrades, 257112
      - Three Comrades Poster [photocopy], [undated]; 257113 (Box 49, Folder 7)